{
    "id": "fbdf93528fdb43ba9035255a631a2af6",
    "title": "Identifying Conditional",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "c8a9bf05408d44faa198207cae5d8f2d",
            "title": "Identifying Conditionals",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "If I don't drink tea in the morning, I feel sick.",
                    "description": "In the zero conditional, we use a simple present tense in both clauses. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "Zero conditional",
                        "First conditional",
                        "Second conditional",
                        "Third conditional"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I will talk to her if I meet her.",
                    "description": "In the first conditional, we use a simple present tense in the if-clause and will + infinitive in the main clause.",
                    "answers": [
                        "Zero conditional",
                        "First conditional",
                        "Second conditional",
                        "Third conditional"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I would have helped him if I had been there.",
                    "description": "In the third conditional, we use a past perfect tense in the if-clause and would have + past participle in the main clause.\r\n\r\n",
                    "answers": [
                        "Zero conditional",
                        "First conditional",
                        "Second conditional",
                        "Third conditional"
                    ],
                    "correct": 3
                },
                {
                    "question": "If I were you I would get that car serviced.",
                    "description": "In the second conditional, we use a simple past tense in the if-clause and would + infinitive in the main clause.",
                    "answers": [
                        "Zero conditional",
                        "First conditional",
                        "Second conditional",
                        "Third conditional"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "I wouldn't be surprised if she got married soon.",
                    "description": "In the second conditional, we use a simple past tense in the if-clause and would + infinitive in the main clause.",
                    "answers": [
                        "Zero conditional",
                        "First conditional",
                        "Second conditional",
                        "Third conditional"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "If he arrives soon, we will go the movies.",
                    "description": "In the first conditional, we use a simple present tense in the if-clause and will + infinitive in the main clause.",
                    "answers": [
                        "Zero conditional",
                        "First conditional",
                        "Second conditional",
                        "Third conditional"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "If I had the time, I would bake a cake.",
                    "description": "In the second conditional, we use a simple past tense in the if-clause and would + infinitive in the main clause.",
                    "answers": [
                        "Zero conditional",
                        "First conditional",
                        "Second conditional",
                        "Third conditional"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "I would have handled the situation differently, if I had been in your place.",
                    "description": "In the third conditional, we use a past perfect tense in the if-clause and would have + past participle in the main clause.",
                    "answers": [
                        "Zero conditional",
                        "First conditional",
                        "Second conditional",
                        "Third conditional"
                    ],
                    "correct": 3
                },
                {
                    "question": "If you had tried harder, you would have succeeded.",
                    "description": "In the third conditional, we use a past perfect tense in the if-clause and would have + past participle in the main clause.",
                    "answers": [
                        "Zero conditional",
                        "First conditional",
                        "Second conditional",
                        "Third conditional"
                    ],
                    "correct": 3
                },
                {
                    "question": "If the team fails, the coach will be held accountable.",
                    "description": "In the first conditional, we use a simple present tense in the if-clause and will + infinitive in the main clause.",
                    "answers": [
                        "Zero conditional",
                        "First conditional",
                        "Second conditional",
                        "Third conditional"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "If you had asked me, I would have told you.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Zero conditional",
                        "First conditional",
                        "Second conditional",
                        "Third conditional"
                    ],
                    "correct": 3
                },
                {
                    "question": "If you had studied at a good college, you might have received a better job offer.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Zero conditional",
                        "First conditional",
                        "Second conditional",
                        "Third conditional"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}